previously on despertae housewives
前情提要
If you're trying  to come between me and my husband,I will take you down
如果你要介入我和我丈夫之间  我不会让你有好日子过
bring it on
谁怕谁
Gaberille threat the nun
Gabriel威胁那个修女
you good to go
你可以走了
Susan hit on her doctoer
Susan向她的医生示好
so you came to ask me out,cause i'll say yes
那你来约我出去 因为我会答应
bree's daughter let her intention being known
Bree的女儿表达了她的意图
it's amazing how far we're willing to go
一件不可思议的事 我们愿意付出多大代价
Andrew,give me one  good reason  why shouldn't  call the police
Andrew，告诉我一个好的理由 为什么我不应当报警
because i'm your son
因为我是你儿子
all in the name of love
都在爱的名义下
If there is one thing Eddie Brit understood,it was nature of war
如果说有一件事为Eddie Brit谙熟 那就是战斗的本性
after two fail marriages and countless rocky  romances
经过两次失败的婚姻 和无数磕磕碰碰的情史
She had learned love was a  battle field
她领悟到爱就是一场战争
it is the easiest way to survive the carnage was total surrender
要在这场血腥中生存 最容易的办法就是举旗投降
i was thinking a vacation of roma will be so romantic
我再考虑一趟去罗马的旅行 将会非常浪漫
Vegas is cheaper
拉斯维加斯要便宜些
could you put yor underwear in the heper
你能不能把你的内裤放进洗衣篮
can you do it   you standing right there
你能代劳吗  就在你旁边
i got a hankering for chinese food tonight
我今晚有点想吃中国菜
i'm so over rice  Let's do pizza
米饭我吃腻了 我们吃比萨
but the day comes for every assaulter  when she must take a stand
对每个处于下风的人都有这么一天 当她必须转守为攻
what do you think you're doing?
你在干什么？
and fight
为自己而战
it's time for my game
该看我的比赛
i want to watch my movie
我要看电影
Eddie,this is important to me
Eddie，这对我很重要
fine
好
i have stuff to do anyway
反正我也有时要做
You see when it came to man,Eddie had a battle plan of her own
你看，每当要对付男人 Eddie总有她的d对策
you have five minutes for Eddie?
能抽5分钟时间陪Eddie吗？
that's some knot  you tied
你真打上结了
yeah? that's no fun it's not tight
是吗？如果不紧就没有乐趣
you know what would be hot,whipped cream
你知道什么会更带劲，生奶油
you're so bad
你真坏
you have no idea
你肯定没见识过
yes,eddie brit understood the nature of war
没错，Eddie深知战斗的本性
Eddie it has been ten minutes
Eddie，已经过了10分钟
Where 's the damn whipped cream
该死的生奶油哪去了
She also know to the victor go the spoils
她也知道只有胜者 才能得到奖赏
Eddie!
the guest bedroom on the second floor of  Whiteapples' house  had the best view in all misteria lane
在整条紫藤街上属Whiteapple家 二楼客房的视野最好
from it's windows one could see Mike Delfino's house one down the street
从那里的窗户，一个人可以看到 Mike Delfino的家在街这一端尽头
all the way to old huber's place one on the other
一直到Huber的住所在另一端
but unfortunately for the room's newest guest
但不幸的是 对这里的新房客来说
the view is about to change,dramatically
他看到的风景将大不如前
What on earth is he doing here?
他在这里干什么？
matthew,go to your room
Matthew，回你房间去
mom and i gonna have a talk now
妈和我要谈谈
he has a room ?have your lost your mind
他有房间？你疯了吗
relax I take newpapers set to the windows people can't see him
别激动,我把报纸粘在窗户上 人们看不到他
kelaget back down there
kela，给我下来
nono we had a talk it's fine he understand what could happen  if he was discovered
不不，我们谈过了 他明白如果他被人发现会有什么后果
for five sec he understand and forget
五秒钟前他还记得 然后就忘了
you know that ?
你知道吗？
we can protect him without treating him like an animal
我可以保护他 不用把他当动物般对待
I'm keeping him safe from the police from the fosters from him themselves
我在保护他，不受警察 姓Foster的，还有他自己的伤害
he is not going back downstairs
他不会再回地下室
Since when do you talk to me like that
从什么时候你开始对我这样讲话
Since i share the risk
从我一道分担风险
i have a few annoucement
我有一些公告需要宣布
I would like to acknowledge Mrs harber for  holding the potluck dinner
我要向Harber女士支援 承担聚餐工作而表示感谢
for hard working
感谢她辛苦的劳动
she is adorable ins't she
她很可爱，是不是？
she is okay
她还行
next saturday the woman's ministration...
下周六女子服务队...
she's gorgeous
小孩真是可爱
knock it off
打住
baby's baby'
小孩小孩小孩
sound  like a broken record     i just had miscarriage
听起来象坏掉的唱片 我才流产不久
it will take some time befor i get ready for  get pregant  again
需要些时间恢复 才能再怀孕
any idea you'll be readyyou know
你觉得你什么时候才会好
stop it
别说了
i just enjoy it the here and now
我只是在这里太无聊
we're together,we have just backed on track  life  is good
我们在一起 我们刚重回正轨，过得很好
before we wrap up,we have a dear friend back form her missionary trip to tell us  about her experiences
我们结束之前  一位亲爱的朋友刚从传教之旅返回 为大家分享她的经历
Sister mary Bernard
Mary Bernard 修女
son of a bitch
狗娘养的！
Daniel
Honey are you in there
你在里面吗
i'm doing homework
我在写作业
really because i'm holding your backpack with all your schoolbooks
真的？因为我手里正拿着你的背包 你的书都在里面
hold on
等等
thanks mom i  was just doing a lttle research on line
多谢，妈 我刚在网上作些调查
I m here mess and grab some  laundry
看你这么乱 我来取一些换洗衣物
pleas not right now
请不要现在
honey stop complaining
不要抱怨
one day you will wish someone offer  to do your laundry
有一天你会祈求某人 能帮你洗衣服
Daniel,question  is there a black man hiding under your bed
Daniel，有个问题 有一个黑人男子藏在你床下吗
what is going on ?
怎么回事？
i just thought you should know i came home to find your song hiding underneath my daughter's bed
我只是觉得应当通知你  今天我回家的时候发现 你儿子藏在我女儿床下
it just seems to me
看起来...
inside,right now
进去，赶快
i apologize  for my son 's behavior it won't happen again
我为我儿子的行为道歉 不会再次发生这样的事
for the house we sell and we're moving
因为我们正在卖房子准备搬走
now,if you excuse me
现在，请原谅
how is it going?
进展如何？
not good
不太好
i'm trying to salvage the pitch from the black frozen yorghout  campaign
我在赶制布莱克冷冻酸奶的 竞标提案
you know what kills me
你知道什么让我头疼
yeah?
什么？
here we are  T-minus 9 hours  eleven minutes from the biggest pitch  in our company's history
现在，还剩9小时11分钟 我们公司有史以来最大规模的提案
and i have nothing even vaguely presentable
我什么都没有 像样的都没
- i will get the coffe
- 我去倒咖啡
thank you
多谢
you wanna go over it   and toss some ideas around
你想重来一遍 让我听听你的想法
no that's okay
不，还好
i know you're exhausted you should go to bed
我知道你很累 你应当去睡觉
come on honey let's do this let's nail this sucker
来,亲爱的,我们一起来做 啃掉这块硬骨头
what do we got
我们手头有什么
we got nothing
什么都没有
okay
好
black frozen yoghourt let you taste bud come in from the cold
布莱克冷冻酸奶 让你的味蕾不再受冷落
okay
好吧
you know whatever i  just knock the rust off  i know i can do better
没关系，我才进入状态 我现在能想出更好的
blacks the froe-yor the make you go wow
布莱克，"冷-优" 让你自然"噢"
come on i'm sorry i just really need focus here
拜托，抱歉 现在我需要集中精力
black frozen yoghourt  beacuse our cows are better
布莱克冷冻酸奶 产自天然好牛
or froghourt
或者  冻爽
froghourt  it's fun to eat fun to say
冻爽  好吃又好听
That 's actually good
确实不错
really?
真的？
no,the cow part that can work
不,关于牛能行
we'll make them characters  we'll humanize them
我们可以创造一些形象 让后赋予他们人性
Oh! i know  i know  celebrity cow spooks people
我想到了想到了,名人 牛，Spooks People
yes that's exactly what i was thinking you know like famouse characters
没错，那正是我想的 就像很有名的形象
like  reworen  Moo
就像Moo
what do you think of that
你觉得如何
thank you i have fabulous time
我过得真愉快
me too
我也是
I guess i'd better get going
我想我该走了
julie is staying in her father's house and i'm all alone here
Julie在他爸那里 我一个人在家
sometimes it actually make me a little nervous
有时会让我有点不安
turn the TV on that 's what i do
把电视打开 我就这么做
oh that's a good idea
很好的主意
I forgot i have a bottle of wine
差点忘了 我有一瓶酒
it's already chilled in the refrigerator
已经放在冰箱里冻好了
i don't know it's just really relax me
我不知道 能让我相当放松
that's good
真不错
so we still good for thursday
那我们礼拜四再约？
yeah
耶
thursday is great
礼拜四有空
good night
晚安
do i just repulse you
我让你感到恶心吗？
no why
不 为什么
we've been on three dates and you just keep acting like a perfect gentleman
我们已经出去过三次  你一直表现得像个完美男士
getting a little odd
变得有点怪怪的
Susan,you make no mistake  i'm like inches away from  ripping off  you clothes right now
Susan你别搞错 我现在不能和你有更进一步的发展
and you stopping why?
为什么不行？
I'm still your doc,it's not quite ethical,yeah
我还是你的医生 那样不符合职业道德
why are we dating
那我们为什么还约会
it's only temporary  once you 're well  i'm done treating you   all bets are  off
只是暂时的，一旦你没事了 我对你的治疗结束，一切都会结束
okay
好吧
what the hell
管它的
okay that's sorta feel unethical
那感觉像不大道德
thank you for meeting with me
感谢你来见我
sure  i didn't invite you to the house  but  the place's real pick site
什么话，我没请你进门 但这个地方也是不错的选择
carlos i'm a nun not a moron
Carlos，我是修女 但我不蠢
i know gab despise me
我知道Gabreil看我不顺眼
she is just jealous that's all
她只是嫉妒 就这样而已
of me,oh,isn't that silly
嫉妒我,是不是太无聊了
she refuse to believe that i can  connect with anyone on a spiritual  level
她不会相信我 能有别的知心女伴
we do have an amazing connection
我们的确算知己
that's why i want to talk to you
也就是为什么我想和你谈话
when i saw you at the church
当我在教堂看到你
i can tell instantly you're unhappy
我一眼就能看出你不快乐
okay,maybe i have been a little  down lately
好吧，也许是最近心情不太好
tell me
告诉我
this whole have no kids thing
一直没有孩子
sister mary i want them so bad
Mary修女 我真的很想要
gab still refuse to give them to you
Gaberiel仍然拒绝为你生孩子
to be fair,she did have  miscarriage recently
公平的说 她最近流产了一次
what if  she decide to agaist kids
万一她以此为借口不再要孩子
what if this just all stalk tacted
万一这都是她一手策划的
that i'm screwed
那我就上当了
sorry
抱歉
you're right
你说得对
you're screwed
你是上当了
unless?
除非？
unless what
除非什么？
american  catholics guide to annulments
美国天主教离婚协议指导
sister mary what is exactly what are you saying here
Mary修女你究竟想说什么
I'm saying god help those who help themselves
我在说上帝帮助那些自助的人
hey,i got great news
我有好消息
we just landed the black frozen yorghout  account
我们刚赢得 布莱克冷冻酸奶的资金
really they love the pitch ?
真的?他们喜欢那个提案？
The talking cows rocking their world
会说话的牛让他们折服
how do they like my bull clinton idea
那他们喜欢我Clinton牛的点子吗
well i rewrote some of  stuff we work on
我重写了我们部分工作
but you know essentially it'sthe same  and they eat it up
但精髓还是一样 他们照单全收
that is fantastic
真是太棒了
finally we can afford hire another executive
我们终于可以 再雇用一格执行主管
terrific,tell me did they like the promtion plan about a bounch of cow eating  contest
太棒了 告诉我他们喜欢那个推销计划吗？
the pitch was running long so we cut off a few things
提案太长 于是我们砍掉了一些东西
I'm just glad they love my idea
我真高兴他们喜欢我的点子
to be fair
当然
do they like the hugh  play cows
他们喜欢以Hugh 和游戏牛吗？
they're calling in for meeting  i gotta go
他们召集开会，我要挂了
i love you bye
爱你，拜
so this is your spleen
这是你的脾脏
normally it would over here because your missing ligament structure
通常它在这里 因为你缺少一些韧带组织
it has wander under over there right  next to the liver
它游动到了这里 就在肝脏隔壁
we discuss about this aftermeaning
我们讨论过后果
every one  thinks you should remove it immediately
每个人都认为你应当立即摘除它
okay
好吧
i guess you guys have all sorts of  new exciting  technians  you don't even cut open the body
我想你们有那些新潮的医学设备  你甚至不需要切开身体
no not really
不，不是的
no?
不是？
so we're talking surgery
那是要做手术？
well i guess i can handle that
我想我可以应付
people got cut  open everyday
每天都有人被切开
so i assume you will let me do the surgery
那么我猜你会让我做这个手术
you ?
你？
it seems natural  i know the most about your case  i promise you will be in very good hands
这很自然 我最了解你的情况  我保证你能得到很好的照料
what?
怎么？
the first time you see me naked  i will be on an operating table
你第一次看到我的身体 是在手术台上
i promise i will be a perfect gentleman my eyes will be strictly on the spleen
我保证我不会有非分之举  我的眼睛一定只会顶着脾脏
docter mrs baker is here for her follow-up
医生，Baker夫人来做复查了
we need to schedule susan for splenectomy,with me
需要为Susan安排胰脏摘除术 我来主刀
Oh,congratulations!
噢,恭喜你!
So I will call you later?
那我等会打电话给你?
Oh,I am so happy for him.He's such a doll.
我真为他高兴.他真的很可爱
I'm curious. Um...
我很好奇. 呃...
why were youso congratulatory?
你怎么那么开心?
Oh,the spleen surgery--
噢,那个脾脏手术--
it'll be his first!
这是他的第一次!
Hey,honey.
嗨,宝贝.
Can we talkabout something?
我能和你讲些事情吗?
Sure.
当然可以.
So I've been thinkingabout the whole baby thing.
我一直在想小孩的事
And how ever long it takes for you to feel ready,I am fine with.
你觉得要多久时间来考虑都可以 我没问题
Okay.
好的.
But here's the deal--
但是情况是这样的--
I need to knowthat this isn't a maybe.
我想确认我们一定会生个孩子 而不是“也许”
I want a promisethat we will have children.
我要你答应我 我们一定会生个孩子
I'm sorry.I can't promise that.
我很抱歉.我不能这样答应你
Why not?
为什么不?
Because I can't saythat I'm gonna wake up tomorrow
因为我不能假定我明早一起床
and suddenly wanna do somethingthat I swore my entire life
就想做一件会改变我人生的事
I would never do. "Maybe" isa very big step for me.
我永远都不想这样. “也许”对我来说已经是个很大的一步
Yeah,well,it isn'tbig enough for me.
是吗,但是,对于我来说还不够大
Well,I'm sorry,but you'rejust gonna have to accept it.
这样子,我很抱歉, 但是你必须得接受这一点
There's nothing else you can do.
你还能怎么样？
That isn'tnecessarily true.
这倒不是真的
Excuse me?
你说什么?
Annulments
婚姻判决无效
You are threatening mewith an annulment?
你用判决无效婚姻来威胁我?
That conniving little bitchput you up to this,didn't she?
那个阴险的小贱人教你这样讲的,对吧?
Didn't she?
是她吗?
This fight could beover right now if you'd justmake me a promise.
如果你愿意给个承诺我 我们现在就根本不用吵架
The only promiseI am making you is that this isso not over.
我现在可以向你承诺的是 这件事没完
hi!
嗨!
Hey.
嘿.
Hi.
嗨.
How's the search coming forthe new ad exec? Any luck?
找到新的广告制作总裁了吗? 有机会吗?
Oh,the pickings are slim.
我们现在的选择不多
So far none ofmy top choices are available.
我的首选都落空了
Hey,um,do you have someonefrom your old company
你能从你的老东家介绍人给我吗?
that you could,you know,maybe recommend?
你能推荐个人给我吗?
Daddy!Well--
爸爸!
I can't find my toothbrush.
我找不到我的牙刷.
I'll be upin a second,buddy.
我马上就上楼来,哥们
Hi.
嗨
As a matter of fact,
事实上
there's this one guy who would be perfect.
我认识一个人可能适合你
Yeah?
谁?
Yeah,hard-working,smart as a whip. Total package.
是一个努力工作,聪明伶俐，干净利落
Really? What's his name?
是吗?他叫什么名字?
Tom.
Tom? Tom what?
Tom? Tom 姓什么?
Tom scavo.
no! No!
不! 不!
I do not think thatthat is a good idea.
我不认为这是个好主意
Come on,honey,I mean,the other nightdoing those pitches--
别这样,宝贝,我的意思是 那天晚上在找灵感的时候
it just gotthe old juices flowing.
应该让过去的事过去了.
I remembered how muchI miss having a real job.
我还记得我多么想要个真正的工作
You have a real job,right herestaying home with the kids.
你的工作就是在家 照顾好孩子
With two incomes,we couldafford a top-notch nanny.
如果我们有两份收入 我们可以请个顶级的保姆
What about penny?
那Penny怎么办?
You're the one who fought foroffice day care. Let's use it.
是你争取到办公室女士权益 我们可以利用这个
What about the two of us workingand living together?
我们一起工作一起生活?
I think that could bea recipe for disaster.
我觉得后果会很恐怖
Why? The last timethat we worked together...
为什么? 上次我们一起工作...
we fell in love.
我们相爱了
Oh,it's just...
噢,只是...
I'M...
我...
I'm not sure that you would findthis job that satisfying.
我只是不确定 你会喜欢这个工作
You don't thinkI'm good enough,do you?
你认为我能力不够,对吗?
I'm not saying that.
我没这样说.
Daddy,I stillcan't find my toothbrush!
爸爸,我还是找不到我的牙刷!
- I'll go.
- 我去拿.
I got it.
我来.
Come on,buddy.Let's hunt it down.
走吧,哥们.我们一起抓住它
So who won the fight?
谁吵赢了?
We weren't fighting.
我们没有吵架.
Mommy's just lettingdaddy know where he stands.
妈妈只是想让爸爸 知道她的立场
Oh,hey! Hey!
噢,嘿! 嘿!
- thanks for coming in,mr. Gainey.
-感谢你的到来,Gainey先生
We'll be in touch.
我们会再联系的
Thank you. Bye.
谢谢你.再见
What did you think?
你觉得怎么样?
Well,honestly,I wasn't blown away.
这样,说实话,我没太满意
I know the pickingsare slim,
我知道挑选的范围很小,
but we can't hold outmuch longer.
但是我们不能这样一直下去了
We need to hiresomeone this week.
这个星期内我们必须招到人
I know! I know! I know.
我知道! 我知道! 我知道.
So who's up next?
下一个是谁?
Tom cavos.You ever heard of him?
Tom Cavos.你听过他吗?
Just... uh...
只是... 有点...
could you excuse mefor just a minute?
对不起，我要离开一下
Sure.
请便.
- Tom cavos?
- Tom Cavos?
Yeah,it's an anagram.
对啊，简写.
It's deceptively simple,don't you think?
满朴素的，不觉得吗?
What do you think you're doing?
你知道你在干什么吗?
I'm going overyour head.
我让你不能理解
I mean,you mightnot think I'm good enough,
我的意思是 也许你认为我不够资格
but maybe ed will bea little more open-minded,
但是也许ED会心胸宽广一点,
since,you know,he's notconstantly competing with me.
因为,你知道, 并不是他一直在和我竞争
You want the truth,tom?
你想听到实话吗,Tom?
I think you're good.You have moments of brilliance.
我认为你很厉害.你有时候机敏过人
But I also thinksometimes you coast.
但是我也认为,有时候你也不在状态
And I thinkif i were your boss
如果我是你的老板
and had to ride your assevery day,
我必须每天盯着你工作,
you would come homeseething with resentment.
这样你每天回家看什么都会带着愤怒
Come on! It's hard enoughkeeping a marriage together.
别这样! 光维持婚姻已经够辛苦的了
If you're at all concernedabout saving our marriage,
如果你不想影响到我们的婚姻,
you better let metake my shot.
你最好让我试一试.
What does that mean?
你这是什么意思?
It means that a little partof me has been hating you
我心里的某一角落开始恨你
ever since you tankedmy promotion at petersen.
自从你上次在petersen害得我不能晋升
Tom...
but I could let it all go ifyou'll give me this one thing.
但是我可以忘记这一切 如果你这次让步
Excuse me.Ed's waiting for you guys.
不好意思. Ed在等你们
Great! Great!
好的! 好的!
Just let my rsumspeak for itself.
让我的简历说话
Uh,just let your rsumspeak for itself?
让你的简历说话?
Yes.
好的.
okay!
好的!
Oh! You workedthe poncer cheese accounts?
噢! “poncer芝士”的案子是你做的?
Those "angry mouse" spots?They were hilarious!
那段“生气的老鼠”? 它们真是棒极了!
I was on thatfrom the beginning.
那案子从一开始就是我做的
warning,do not eat the cheese!
警告,不要吃那些芝士!
The cheese is evil!
芝士是魔鬼!
I love that!
我喜欢那一段!
You've got a great rsum?Thank you.
你的简历让人印象深刻
Yeah,gosh,it is.It's quite impressive.
是的，天啊，正是. 我很有印象
Oh,wow,I see you workedfor bellfore and barrasso.
噢,你以前在bellfore和barrasso做过
That's a great shop.
他们很不错.
Yeah,I put my time in.
是的,我花了很多时间
Uh-huh,and when were you there?
这样,你是什么时候在那里的?
Because you forgot to list your dates of employmentfor that one.
因为你忘记写就职日期了
Um,that wasa few years back.
因为,那些是几年前的事了
Uh-huh. And how longdid you stay?
这样.你在他们那里待了多久?
Just about five months,actually.
准确的来说,大概5个月
What,did you getrecruited by another firm?
什么? 没别的公司聘请你吗?
Did somebodycherry-pick ya?
你被人挖角了吧?
No,I was fired.
不,我是被炒掉的.
Yeah,but honestly,I was happy to leave
但是,老实说,能离开我很高兴
because they didn't getmy sense of humor.
因为他们体会不了我的幽默
I actually pitched a version of the "cheese is evil"there first.
最开始是我想到“芝士是魔鬼”那一段
They hated it.
但是他们不喜欢.
Idiots!Well,their loss,right?
笨蛋!那是他们的损失,对吗?
That was very cool.
那很酷哦.
So did you do that solo?
那段独白是你一个人做的?
Actually,no. My wifehelped me on that one.
不是的.我的妻子帮我的
Um,she's inadvertising,too.
哦,她也是从事广告业的
But if you were to ask her,
但是如果你去问她的话,
I'm sure she'd tell you she did the whole thing all by herself.
我肯定她会说那一段 都是她做的
credit hog,huh?I know the type.
贪婪荣誉?我知道那一型
You know what,tom?I like you.
Tom,你知道吗?我喜欢你
Ed...
and I'm not usually onefor hiring in the room.
我通常不会在办公室内就决定雇人
No,no,no,no,we never hire in the room.
不，不，不 我们从来不在办公室内雇人
But we're in a time crunch,and we need someone now.
但我们现在缺乏时间， 并且我们现在就需要人
I think you're the guy.
我想你就是那个人
Lynette,you got any issues?
Lynette,你有什么问题吗？
Well...
恩...
um,let me just call ina few references
在我们签订任何正式的文件前
before we makeanything official.
先给我一些参考资料
Sure! Sure!We'll be in touch,okay?
当然！当然！ 我会联系你的，好吗？
the cheese is evil!
芝士是魔鬼！
Oh,god,I love that.
上帝，我爱那个
Oh,um,I'm lookingfor father crowley.
我找Crowley神父
Do you know where he is?
你知道他在哪吗？
Um,he's inthe confessional.
他在忏悔室
How long has it beensince your last confession?
你上次忏悔是多久以前？
Who cares?
谁在乎？
Father,it's me.
神父，是我
Gabrielle?
Yeah.
是我
Look,I need youto do something for me.
听着，我需要你为我做件事
I need you to get rid ofsister mary bernard.
我要你把修女Mary Bernard赶走
What? Why?
什么？为什么？
Because she's ruiningmy marriage.
因为她正在破坏我的婚姻
- Sister mary?
- mary修女？
Yes!
没错！
At first it startedwith the love letters while he was in prison,
开始时当他在监狱时他们互通情书
and the next thing I know,
接下来我所知道的就是
they're spendingday and night together--
他们不论白天晚上都在一起--
sneaking offto private bible study,
偷偷摸摸的秘密学习圣经
- and one-on-onespiritual consultation.
- 还有一对一的心理咨询
Gabrielle--
and if that wasn't enough,he issaying her name in his sleep.
如果那些还不够的话 他在梦中喊她的名字
"hold me,sister mary,hold me."
"抱住我，mary修女，抱住我"
it's disgusting.He's like a lovesick puppy.
让人恶心 他就像是患了相思病的小狗
do you have reasonto believe that your husbandand sister mary are...
你有什么理由认为 mary修女和你丈夫...
having sex?
上过床？
Speak from the heart,gabrielle.
说心里话，gabrielle
This is just betweenme,you and god.
这里只有你，我和上帝
Yeah... yep.They're having sex.
是...是的，他们上过床
Carlos confessedeverything...
Carlos承认了一切...
right beforehe asked for an annulment.
就在他提出要申请婚姻无效之前
forgive me,father,for I have sinned.
原谅我，神父 我有罪
How long sinceyour last confession?
你上一次忏悔是多久以前？
Mm,not that long ago.
不是很久
Look,I sorta told a fib,so...
听着，我可以说是撒了一个谎， 所以...
how many "hail marys"is that gonna set me back?
多少次的“万福玛利亚” 可以让我得到宽恕？
- oh,honey.
- 亲爱的
Go away!
走开！
Oh,honey,what happenedwasn't my fault.
亲爱的，那不是我的错
There's no way I could'vepredicted how betty would react.
我不可能预测出betty对这件事的反应
Oh,please,you knewsomething bad would happen.
算了吧 你知道会有糟糕的事发生
You wanted all thisto blow up in my face.
你希望这些让我颜面扫地
Oh,honey,why would I want that?
亲爱的 我怎么会那样想
Because you're jealous thatmy life's just getting started
因为你嫉妒我的生活正在开始
and yours is over.
而你的却结束了
Danielle,that's ridiculous,sweetheart.
Danielle,那太可笑了，亲爱的
Daddy's dead.
爸爸死了
You drove your boyfriendto suicide.
你逼得你的男朋友自杀了
You're getting olderby the minute,
你每一分钟都在变老
and soon you'll beso dried up and bitter
很快你就会变得又干又老
that no man will ever wantto touch you ever again.
再也不会有男人想要碰你一下
Danielle...
and now you're determinedto ruin my life
所以现在你决定要毁了我的生活
so I have to stay with you hereand keep you company
我得在你变成化石的时候
while you turninto an old fossil.
一直待在这里和你做伴
All I ever wanted wasfor you to be happy.
我所有想要的就是能让你开心快乐
Don't just want it.Make it happen.
不要只是想，让它变成现实
danielle,I don't feel muchlike cooking tonight.
danielle,我今晚不是很想煮饭
I'm thinkingof ordering a pizza.
我想订pizza
I want canadian bacon.
我要加拿大培根味的
Please.
谢谢
All right.
好的
He's mad at you'cause you hit him.
他对你很生气 因为你打了他
Well,I feel bad about that.
好吧，我对那也很抱歉
But when I considerthe risks he was taking...
但我一想到他所冒的危险...
it's a shamehe can't see that girl.
他不能再见那女孩真是个遗憾
She's so pretty.
她那么漂亮
What did you sayabout danielle?
你说danielle什么？
I said that she...
我说她...
you know I don't want youthinking about things like that.
你知道我不想你想那些事情
I'm sorry.I didn'T. I'm sorry.
对不起，我没有，对不起
It's okay. It's okay.
没事，没事了
Go on and run upto your room.
上楼跑回你的房间
Read the comics I got you.
去看那些我给你的漫画
And,caleb?
还有，caleb？
If I ever catch you lookingat that van de kamp girl,
如果再让我逮到 你在看那个Van de kamp家的女孩
I'll hit you twice as hardas I hit your brother,
就像揍你兄弟一样 我会加倍力狠命揍你
and I won't feel bad about it.
而且我心里不会愧疚的
Okay?
明白了吗?
Okay.
知道了
So this wholesplenectomy thing--
那么这整件脾切除术的事情--
you feelgood about it,huh?
你感觉很好 不是么?
Yeah,yeah,I told you.It's a routine surgery.
没错 是的 我告诉过你 这是常规手术
You're gonna be fine.
你会没事的
Right,right.
当然 当然
Actually,I sort of meant,um...
其实 我的意思是...
do you personallyfeel confident?
你自己有信心吗?
What do you mean?
你什么意思?
Well,you know,you're gonna be...
恩 就是说 你就要...
hacking into me,
剖开我
and I just wanted to make surethat you feel ready.
我只是想确认一下你准备好了
I've never taken outa spleen before.
我还没有取过脾
But believe me,it's no big deal.
但是请相信我 这不是件什么大事情
Spleen,gallbladder,it's all the same.
脾 胆囊都一样
Okay,red flag! See,I didn't go to medical school,
好了 别说了 你知道我没去过医学院上课
but I'm thinking, not all the same.
可我在想, 不是都一样的吧
Susan,I know what I'm doing.You're gonna have to trust me.
Susan 我知道我在做什么 你要相信我
I would like to.But I gotta be honest--
我也想啊 可我得说实话--
the fact that you can't evencut that steak isn't helping.
--- 你连牛扒都不会切
That's not fair.You overcooked it,
话不能这么说 是你煮得太熟了
and,frankly,it's not the freshest meat.
老实说 这肉的确不新鲜
Well,neither am I.I've got 35 years on that cow.
我也不新鲜了 我都35岁了
Wait,susan,are you saying you don't want meto be your surgeon?
等等 susan 你是想说 你不想要我给你动手术?
I'm sorry.
真是抱歉
I don't mean this to soundthe wrong way. I just...
我不想让你误会 我只是...
I would be more comfortablewith an experienced surgeon.
如果有个有经验的外科医生的话 我会更安心一点
That's okay. I understand.
没关系 我理解
Thank you.
谢谢你
I should really be going.
我真的要走了
What?
什么?
I didn't evenserve dessert yet.
我连甜品都还没上
You said you understood!
可你说你可以理解的
No,I do,I do.I respect your decision to see another doctor,
对 我可以理解 真的 我尊重你的决定 去看另外一个医生
You need to respectthat my feelings are hurt.
但是你知道吗? 你要明白 我的自尊心受到伤害了
What? You want me to putmy life on the line to service your ego?
什么? 你要我为了你的自尊心 而把整条命都给赌上?
I save lives every day.I cut. I save. I cut. I save.
我每天都拯救生命 我解剖 我救人 我解剖 我救人
That's what I do,and if that gives me an out-of-control ego,
这是我的工作 如果你硬要认为我自尊心太强的话
well,maybe I need that to cut intoanother human being.
也许 我需要这种自尊心来让我 有勇气给其他人做手术
jim...
Dinner's ready.
晚餐好啦
So did you call around?Check on my references?
你查过我的背景资料了吗?
I told edyou were my husband,
我跟ed说你是我的老公
and he was cool with that.
他说这对他来说没问题
He really wants to hire you.
他是真的想聘请你
So who am ito stand in the way?
那么我干吗要挡你的道呢?
Really? So I got the job?
真的? 那么我得到那份工作了?
On one condition.
只要你答应一个条件
If you take this job,
如果你接受这份工作
you are never allowedto bring up
你不能谈论任何有关
what happened beforewith your promotion.
你以前那次升职的事情
That's it? Deal.
就这么简单? 说定了
No,it's not a deal.I need a solemn vow
不 还没说定呢 我要你一本正经地发誓
that you will never throwthat in my face ever again.
你从此都不会再跟我提这件事
Because if you do,you will unleash demons
如果你提的话，后果会很严重
that you do not wanna meet.
你不会想看到事情发展成那样
I get it.
明白了
And what i really need from you...
我真的很需要...
is to be forgiven.
你的原谅
Actually,I already haD.
其实 我早就原谅你了
This dinner is really good.
晚餐真好
Thank you.
谢谢你
多谢
- Hi,betty.
- 好啊 betty.
Hello.
好
I wanted to talk to youabout what happened the other day with the kids.
我想跟你谈谈那天孩子们的事情
I told you,we will be moving soon.
我跟你说过了 我们就快搬家了
There's nothingto worry about.
没有什么再要担心的了
Well,my fear is thatif we keep them apart,
恩 我所害怕的是 如果我们分开他们俩
they'll try that much harderto be together.
他们会更加接近全力地想在一起
I mean,you knowhow teenagers can be,and,
我的意思是 你知道年轻人 会作出什么样的事情 而且
well,a lot can happenin a couple of weeks.
几个星期之内 可以发生很多事情
I'll make a deal with you.
我想跟你订个协议
If you control yours,I will control mine.
你管好你的 我管好我的
Well,how about someold-fashioned chaperoning?
那么，老式的伴护怎么样吗?
That way they can,um,still see each other,
那样的话 恩 他们还可以看到对方
and we won't have tobe the villains.
我们也不需要当恶人了
When it comesto my son's best interests,
为了我儿子着想
I'm not afraid of beingthe villain.
我愿意当恶人
I assumed that you wouldfeel the same way,bree.
我想 你也是这么觉得的 bree
Now that you mention it,I guess I do.
既然你这么说了 我想我也是这么觉得的
I have to go. I have some,um,muffins in the oven.
我要走了 还有些松饼在烤炉呢
Mom,what's wrong?
妈 怎么啦?
It's the applewhites. I don't want you to go near them.
是applewhites一家 我不想你去接近他们
What?!
什么?!
Do you remember the manthey arrested--
你还记得那个被捕的人吗--
the one that brokeinto gabrielle's
那过闯入gabrielle家
and escapedfrom the mental hospital?
从精神病院逃出来的?
He's there.
他就在那里
I saw him in their window.They're hiding him.
我在他们的窗子瞧见他 他们藏匿着他
You're kidding.No,I'm not.
你在开玩笑吧 不 我没有
And I forbid youto go over there.
我不允许你去那里
Lynette,hi,it's bree.Uh,listen,
Lynette 你好 我是bree 恩 听好了
call me when youget this message,
当你接到这个信息的时候 打电话给我
and please cometo poker tonight.
今天晚上过来打牌吧
I have some big newsabout the applewhites.
我有关于applewhites一家的大新闻
All right,bye.
就这样 再见
Who was that?
是谁啊?
Sister mary.
mary修女
They just transferred her toa parish in fairbanks,alaska.
他们刚刚把她转到另一个教区 在费尔班克斯 阿拉斯加
You're kidding me. Why?
你在跟我说笑吧 为什么?
She doesn't know.
她也不知道
The diocese wouldn't evengive her a reason.
主教教区也没有告诉她原因
Ah,vatican politics.
罗马教廷的政治
What's wrong?
有什么不对劲吗?
I think I'm just coming downwith a migraine.
我觉得我突然有点偏头痛
Oh,well,maybe youshould go lie down.
哦 可能你需要躺一下才好
I'm gonna be outfor a while.
我要出去一下
All right.
好的
Uh,I'll see you there.
恩 回头见
Susan?What are you doing here?
Susan? 你在这里干什么?
We need to talk.
我们需要谈谈
Okay,all right,but,look,I just got out of surgery.
可以 好的 但是 我刚刚做了手术
I've been waitingfor three hours.
我等了你3个小时了
After you stormed outthe other night,
自从那晚你生气地走了以后
I started to doubt myself.
我开始质疑自己
I started to think,
我开始想
"gee,you know,maybe I shouldjust ignore my better instincts,
"天 可能我真的不能太相信直觉
and I should let dr. Ron gut me like a fish."
我应该让Ron医生 像解剖一条鱼一样给我做手术"
- Susan--
I mean,why not?
我的意思是 为什么不试试呢?
'Cause all my life,
一直以来 在我的生活里
I have jumped through hoopsto keep men from leaving.
我竭尽全力不要男人离开我
But I'm not doing it anymore.So tough luck,pally.
可我不会再这样了 不走运而已 亲爱的
You just missed outon a good thing.
你自己没有把握住
Susan...
you've been herefor three hours?
你在这里等了3个小时?
Yeah.Well,two hours ago,
是啊 2个小时以前
flowers,champagneand an apology note were deliveredto your doorstep.
你的门前送去了花 香槟 道歉卡片
Really?
是么?
Look,I put our relationshipat risk,all right?
是我令我们的关系陷入危机 知道了吗?
And it was stupid.
那很愚蠢
I haven't felt this wayabout somebody in a long time.
我很久没有对别人有这样的感觉了
Susan,I really like you.
Susan 我真的很喜欢你
And because of that,I...
正因为如此 我...
I can't be your doctor,let alone,your surgeon.
我不能当你的医生 更不用说 当给你动手术的外科医生了
I mean,there's a pretty good reason why they make those rules.
我是想说 他们定这样的规定 的确有道理
Listen,I hopeyou forgive me,all right?
听好了 我希望你可以原谅我 可以吗?
Because I'll hate myselfif I lose you.
如果失去你 我会恨透我自己的
I wouldn't want youto hate yourself.
我可不想你恨自己
No.
不
And I am so sorryabout that... snap thing.
对于... 那小菜一碟的事情 我很抱歉
I was just tryingto be theatrical.
我只是想扮的戏剧化一点
I got your note.What's going on?
我收到你的纸条了 发生什么事情了?
Are you hidingsomeone in your house?
你在你的房子藏了什么人吗?
What?
什么?
My mom saw someone inyour second-story window.
我妈在你家2楼的窗户里看到什么人了
She thinks it's the guywho broke into mrs. Solis'.
她认为是那个闯进Solis夫人家的家伙
Damn it,caleb.
见鬼 caleb
Is that his name?
那是他的名字吗?
Has she told anybody else?
她有跟其他人说过吗?
She left messageson her friends' machines.
她给她的朋友们留言了
They're coming oversoon to get details.
她们马上就会过来详听细节
We're gonna have to leave tonight.
今晚我们必须离开
- This is--
- 这是--
why? What's going on?
为什么? 发生什么事了?
I would loveto tell you,believe me,I would.
我很想告诉你 相信我 我真得很想告诉你
But I can'T.
但是爱莫能助
If you trust me,I could help you.
如果你相信我 我可以帮你
My familyhas secrets,too.
我家也有秘密
What my brother did--
我哥曾经--
it's bad.
很糟糕
Last year my brotherdid something really awful,
去年 我兄弟作了件很不好的事情
and my parentscovered it up for him.
我父母帮他收场了
If anyone were toever find out,
如果被任何人发现的话
andrew and my momcould go to jail.
andrew和我妈要去蹲监狱了
So you don't have to worryabout me judging you.
所以你不用担心 我不会对你妄下定论的
Tell me your secrets.I'll understand.
告诉我你的秘密,我会理解的
Okay.
好吧
But you tell meyours first.
但你得先告诉我你的秘密
What are you doing here?
你来这儿干吗?
I heard you werebeing transferred so I cameto say good-bye.
我听说你要调走,所以来道别
Come to gloatis more like it.
没见过这么心满意足的人
No,we've hadour differences,
不,我们是有不同
but that doesn't meanI'm happy to see you shipped off to alaska.
但并不是说 你被送到alaska去我会很开心
Brr.
磅！
You had something to dowith this,didn't you?
这事肯定与你有关,对吧?
Me? Oh,I'm justa humble sinner.
我? 哦,我只是个可怜的罪人
You're the one withall the power around here--
你才是权力无边的人
all the... annulment mojo.
什么判决无效婚姻
Is that why you did it?
这就是为什么你要这样做?
Well,getting rid of meisn't gonna change anything.
好吧,把我赶走也无济于事
Carlos will do what he wants.
Carlos还是会做他想做的
The problems in your marriagearen't going away.
你们婚姻中的问题也不会消失
Maybe not...
或许不会...
but you certainly are.
可是你走定了
You missed a spot.
你输了
That was a mistake.
你犯了个错
There.I think we're all done here.
好了,我想我们到此为止
Oh,my god!Oh,my god! Hold on!
哦,天哪!天哪!天哪!别动!
Are you okay?
你没事吧?
Stop fighting!
住手!
Stop fighting! No!
住手! 别打了!
What the hellwere you thinking?
你到底怎么想的?
Uh,depends.What have you heard?
哦,这要看...你都听到些什么?
I got a callfrom the church.
我接到了教堂的电话
They said you attackedsister mary.
他们说你袭击了mary修女
Yeah,that's about right.
是的,差不多是这样
What are you thinking?
你在想些什么?
I wasn't,but I was thinkingabout it on the way over here.
我没想什么,但是 在回来的路上我确实想了
And I realized the assI should be kicking is yours.
而且我觉得我该扁的人是你
- Mine?
- 我?
Yes!
是的!
Sister mary manipulated youinto threatening me,
mary修女操纵你威胁我
but you're the idiotthat fell for it.
而你是个甘于被人操纵的傻瓜
I was notthreatening you.
我没有威胁你
I was asking for a promise.
我只是要一个承诺
You made me a promise,carlos,
你给过我承诺,carlos
a long time ago--till death do us part.
很久以前,“直到死亡将我们分开”
And one day you just come homeand start throwing words around like annulment.
然后有一天你一回家 就开始围绕无效婚姻开始大放厥词
How do you thinkthat makes me feel?
你认为我会怎么想?
Okay,I'm sorryabout that.
好吧,对此我很抱歉
I need to have a child.
我想要个孩子
And I need to knowI'm the woman you want to spendthe rest of your life with,
可我想知道 我是不是你想一起共度余生的女人
not just some uterusin high heels.
而不只是个穿着高跟鞋的生殖机器
Gabrielle,please--
Gabrielle,求你了--
no,carlos,I am sorry.
不,carlos,对不起
I am not gonna be blackmailedinto giving birth.
我不想被人威胁着生孩子
You have to choose.
你必须做出选择
And I wish you would do itso I can move on with my life.
而且我希望你做出正确的选择 我的生活才能继续
Well,of course I choose you.
好吧,我当然选择你
I think that'sthe right decision.
我想那是正确的选定
You know,I made a decision,too.
你知道,我也做了决定
The answer to your questionearlier is yes.
你提出的问题,答案是"是"
Yes...
是...
I wanna have a baby.
我想要个孩子
I wanna havea baby with you.
我想和你要个孩子
betty.
betty
What a surprise.
真让人吃惊
Can I talk to youfor a moment?
我能和你谈一会儿吗?
Uh,now is actuallynot a good time for me.
哦,这会儿时间不对
I think it is.
我觉得很对
I wanted to chat with you before you didsomething foolish.
我想在你做出蠢事之前和你谈谈
I don't knowwhat you mean.
我不明白你的意思
The person you sawat my house today
你今天在我家见到的人
is my other son.
是我的另一个儿子
His name is caleb.
他叫caleb
He didn't harm gabrielle,
他没有伤害gabrielle
and he didn't hurtthe man in the car trunk.
而且他也没伤害车箱里的人
That's all you need to know.
这就是你得明白的
He's your son?
他是你儿子?
He's my dear sonwho happens to be slow.
他是我的乖儿子,有时候他反应迟钝
Sometimes he makes mistakes.
有时候他犯点小错
But,betty,the policeare looking for him.
可是,betty,警察在找他
He escaped from that facilitythey sent him to.
他逃跑了
He had help,trust me.
他有帮手,相信我
I've always thoughtthe maternal instinct
我一直认为母性的本能
is one ofnature's most amazing gifts.
是自然界最神奇的天赋
I mean,the length thatsome mothers will go to to protect their children--
我的意思是,一个母亲 要保护他的孩子的欲望
it drives ordinary womento do extraordinary things,
会让一个普通的女人 做出不普通的事情
women like me,bree,and like you.
象我这样的女人, 包括象bree你这样的女人
What are you talking about?
你在说什么啊?
If you breathe one wordof caleb's existence to anyone,
如果你把caleb的事告诉别人
I will tell carlos,gabrielle and the police
我会告诉carlos,gabrielle还有警察
that it was your sondriving the car
是你的儿子开的车
that killed juanita solis
撞死了juanita solis
and that you have been coveringup his crime ever since.
而且你一直瞒着这事儿
We're going to begreat friends,bree.
我们会成为好朋友,bree
We have so much in common.
我们有太多的共同点
So is that all she said?
她就是这么说的?
Yeah,something aboutthe applewhites.
是啊,applewhites家的事
I'm dying of curiosity.
我要好奇死了
it's rude to keeppeople waiting.
让客人等是不礼貌的
Hi. Come on in.
嗨,请进
So,spill it.
那么,透露一下吧
What's the scoopon the applewhites?
applewhites家什么事?
Um,about that... um...
恩,这个吗...恩...
oh,bree,come on,dish already!
哦,bree,快点,盘子都准备好了!
Well,perhaps I gotmore excited than I should have,
好吧,或许比我已知的还要好
but I recently found outthat betty applewhite
我最近发现betty applewhite
is quite the poker player,
是个打牌的好手
and so,uh,I have invited herto join our weekly game.
所以,哦,我请他加入我们的周末聚会
Hello,everybody.
大家好
I hope you broughtyour checkbooks because I am feeling lucky.
但愿你们都带了支票本来 因为我感觉今天手气很好
Everyone understands the nature of war.
所有人都明白战争规律
I raise.
我跟
We also understand that victory depends on the cards
我们也明白胜利
that we have been dealt.
得靠我们打出去的牌
Some,when faced with a bloody battle,
有些人,面对一场血战的时候
simply give in.
会草草放弃
But for some,surrender is unacceptable.
但对有些人,投降是不可接受的
Well,bree,what are you gonna do?
好吧,bree,你打算怎么办?
Even though they know it will be a fight...
即使他们知道将会是一场...
I'll raise you.
我也跟
...To the death.
...死战